{
    "learn-french": {
        "flashcards": [
            {
                "question": "Hello!/Hola!",
                "answer": "bonjour!"
            },
            {
                "question": "A boy./ Un niño.",
                "answer": "un garçon"
            },
            {
                "question": "A girl./ Luna niña",
                "answer": "une fille"
            },
            {
                "question": "The boy eats./ El niño come.",
                "answer": "le garçon mange"
            },
            {
                "question": "The boy drinks./ El niño bebe.",
                "answer": "le garçon boit"
            },
            {
                "question": "La niña come./ The girl eats.",
                "answer": "la fille mange"
            },
            {
                "question": "A woman/ Una mujer.  ",
                "answer": "une femme"
            },
            {
                "question": "A man./ Un hombre.",
                "answer": "un homme"
            },
            {
                "question": "The woman drinks./ La mujer bebe.",
                "answer": "la femme boit"
            },
            {
                "question": "The man drinks./ El hombre bebe. ",
                "answer": "le homme boit"
            },
            {
                "question": "The woman eats./ La mujer come.",
                "answer": "la femme mange"
            },
            {
                "question": "The girl drinks./ La niña bebe.",
                "answer": "la fille boit"
            },
            {
                "question": "The boys./ Los niños.",
                "answer": "des garçons"
            },
            {
                "question": "The dog./ El perro.",
                "answer": "le chien"
            },
            {
                "question": "The boy runs./ El nino corre.",
                "answer": "le garçon court"
            },
            {
                "question": "The man runs./ El hombre corre.",
                "answer": "le homme court"
            },
            {
                "question": "The man read./ El hombre leyo.",
                "answer": "le homme lit"
            },
            {
                "question": "The woman read. / La mujer leyo.",
                "answer": "la femme lit"
            },
            {
                "question": "The woman eats / La mujer come.",
                "answer": "la femme mange"
            },
            {
                "question": "Los ninos comen./ The boys eat.",
                "answer": "les garçons mangent"
            },
            {
                "question": "The girls drink./ Las ninas beben.",
                "answer": "les filles boivent"
            },
            {
                "question": "Las ninas corren. The girls run.",
                "answer": "les filles courent."
            },
            {
                "question": "Las mujeres corren. The women run.",
                "answer": "les femmes courent."
            },
            {
                "question": "The girl drinks her fruit juice.",
                "answer": "la fille boit du jus de fruit"
            },
            {
                "question": "Los hombres. The men.",
                "answer": "des hommes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Las mujeres. / The women",
                "answer": "des femmes"
            },
            {
                "question": "El nino camina. / The boy walks.",
                "answer": "le garçon marche"
            },
            {
                "question": "Las ninas. / The girls",
                "answer": "des filles"
            },
            {
                "question": "El come. / He eats.",
                "answer": "il mange"
            },
            {
                "question": "Los ninos comen./ The boys eat.",
                "answer": "les garçons mangent"
            }
        ]
    }
}